http://www.metallisation.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Our Website Privacy Policy tells you what will happen to any personal data that you provide to us as a result of using this website. The Policy is available here: (7) Website Privacy Policy The information is written for the benefit of general visitors to the website as well as new and existing customers.
Our Use of Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics to monitor how our website is being used so we can make improvements. Our use of Google Analytics requires us to pass to Google your IP address (but no other information) – Google uses this information to prepare site usage reports for us, but Google may also share this information with other Google services. In particular, Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Related information:
Our Website Privacy Policy tells you what will happen to any personal data that you provide to us as a result of using this website. The Policy is available here: (7) Website Privacy Policy The information is written for the benefit of general visitors to the website as well as new and existing customers.
Our Use of Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics to monitor how our website is being used so we can make improvements. Our use of Google Analytics requires us to pass to Google your IP address (but no other information) – Google uses this information to prepare site usage reports for us, but Google may also share this information with other Google services. In particular, Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Related information:
Google’s privacy policy
How Google uses this information
Scroll To Top
